http://www.standard-industrial.com/privacy-policy.html

Metal Fabrication EquipmentHomeAbout UsContact Us
Call: 662.624.2436Fax: 662.624.2581 Email: vance@standard-industrial.com
Online CatalogCustom CapabilitiesPortfolio GalleryParts Warranty PoliciesCareersFAQSRequest for Quote
ProductsPress BrakesHydraulic ShearsHydraulic PressesCNC Back GaugesCustom Metal
Fabrication EquipmentCustom Hydraulic PressesCustom ShearsIn-House and On-Site Maintenance ServicesGovernment
Inquires WelcomeGSA RegisteredHUB Zone certifiedLongtime supplier of
U.S. Govt. facilities all
over the worldPortfolio GalleryStraightening PressesTravel Frame PressesSpecial Presses by Standard
Email This Page
Privacy PolicyStandard Industrial Company respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via vance@standard-industrial.com or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only Standard Industrial Company's website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Standard Industrial Company is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.Cookies
Standard Industrial Company's website does not use cookies. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Standard Industrial Company may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Standard Industrial Company reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of Standard Industrial Company and is effective as of August 31, 2012. This statement does not create an agreement between Standard Industrial Company and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.Contact Us:
Standard Industrial Company
1410 Industrial Park Drive
Clarksdale, MS. 38614
Phone: 662.624.2436
Fax: 662.624.2581
Email: vance@standard-industrial.com
Website: www.standard-industrial.com
Standard Industrial Company
Phone: 662.624.2436     Fax: 662.624.2581     Email: vance@standard-industrial.comwww.standard-industrial.comPrivacy Policy     Site Map
© 2020, Standard Industrial CompanySite created by Thomas Web Solutions and powered by Navigator Platform
